http://www.unionleader.com/site/privacy.html

Manchester, NH
(03109)
Today
Sunshine and clouds mixed. High 47F. Winds light and variable..
Tonight
Mostly cloudy. Low 28F. Winds light and variable.
Public Notices
Privacy StatementThe Union Leader Corporation and its affiliates collect, use, store, and share information obtained from users of UnionLeader.com and NewHampshire.com (referred to in this policy as "Union Leader").Union Leader collects information from users at several different points on our websites. For example, we request personal information from users at the time of any registration and on order forms such as subscriptions, wherein a user provides information such as name, address, e-mail address, phone number, credit card or other billing information.UnionLeader.com does not provide credit card or billing information to outside third parties, other than as necessary for credit card and billing processing by service providers prohibited from using the information provided to them in any other way, or sharing or selling the information.Union Leader may share personal information with third party vendors and service providers like email distributors, list processors, analysts, and promoters. Only information necessary for these third parties’ services is provided, and they are prohibited from sharing or reselling the information.Personal information such as name, address, email, and telephone number may also be shared with our partners and advertisers in connection with promotions such as contests, sweepstakes, or special offers, should you decide to participate in such promotions or contests.Union Leader uses personal information to communicate with you. You may receive e-mail messages alerting you when the website is updated with breaking news, or other information or offers that may be of interest to you. You can opt out of this service at any time by sending a message to the webmaster.Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on Union Leader Corporation and relating to our Web site.Union Leader may also collect and share with third parties like vendors, service providers, advertisers, and marketing partners aggregate information such as age, town, ZIP code, gender, whether you read the print edition, and other non-personal information about the device or computer used to access our sites, such as IP address, browser type, browsing history, language, and other transactional information, including geolocation information. This helps us provide useful content and services and it gives our advertisers, who make this site possible, a better understanding of who they reach by advertising with Union Leader.For example, visitor traffic is logged so we can count user sessions, identify our customer base and make improvements to meet user preferences. Non-personal information is collected to help us better serve our readers and advertisers. Clicks from an advertiser's banner or tile to that advertiser's website are logged and reported to the advertiser. No personally identifiable information is collected in these operations.CookiesRegistration results in a cookie being stored on the user's computer. A cookie is a small data file that is used solely to identify you as a repeat visitor so you are not asked to register again. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.Your Web browser must have cookies enabled to view articles on Union Leader’s websites or to view Union Leader archives at NewsBank. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of websites you visit. If you delete cookies from your Web browser, you will need to re-submit the registration form to read articles on the site.Some of our business partners (advertisers, news/information providers) use cookies if you click to their site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.Log filesLike most standard website servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.LinksThis Web site contains links to other sites. For example, purchase of archive article(s) requires an account and a credit card transaction with NewsBank Inc., and is subject to terms and conditions of NewsBank.Please be aware that the Union Leader Corporation is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.Notification of changesIf we change our privacy or registration policy on this Web site that further affects information we gather, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.Contact informationIf users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact the digital@unionleader.com.
Most Popular
Articles
Images
Videos
Collections
ArticlesMan claims NH Lottery owes him a gold bar, or $750,000NH House Speaker died of COVID-19Nor'easter to bring heavy snow, strong winds to NHCOVID-19 clusters identified at two more Manchester schoolsDefiant Belknap County Delegation defies mask orderManchester school board hands out raises to top executivesHampton woman dies in Seabrook rolloverTownhouse development to be built in NashuaEx-deputy chief's suit seeks $1M-plus from Salem resident who complainedEight with COVID-19 had visited Manchester casino; Keene, Seabrook exposures too
Images
Videos
CollectionsSnowstorm, Dec. 5NH Legislature Organization Day, Dec. 2Div. I Football Championship, Nov. 21Div. II Football Championship, Nov. 21Christmas Parade, Concord, Nov. 21Division III & IV Football Championships, Nov. 14
© Copyright 2020 Union Leader Corp., 100 William Loeb Drive Manchester, NH | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
<]
